dealfish.co.ug 2012-05-04

# Privacy policy (UPDATED) • Dealfish.co.ug

  * » Privacy policy (UPDATED)

#### Legal policy

  1. MIHIA reserves the right to contact and send information to Users using the contact details (including email address and mobile phone number) provided to MIHIA. In this regard you undertake to ensure that such details are up to date and to inform us of any change in your contact details. MIHIA will not be liable for information being sent to out of date contact details. 
  2. Children below 18 years of age should not access the Site or use the Service. MIHIA does not have any intention of collecting any personally identifiable information from individuals under 18 years of age. If you are aware that a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, please contact us and we will remove the information. 
  3. The security of the information that you provide to us is important to us. To prevent unauthorized disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have in place reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure any information we collect online. 
  4. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. When using a shared computer, be sure to sign off and do not opt to stay logged in to dealfish. Should you realize that you accidentally allowed a third party to access your account, you must let us know immediately, as you may be held liable for their actions in your name. 
  5. We do not have any control over the privacy practices of any external websites linked from the main www.dealfish.co.za domain. 
  6. Third party advertisers may collect certain information that is available to them through your interaction with their advertisements. MIHIA has no control or knowledge as to their practices and it is suggested that you read their privacy policy separately before clicking on any advertisements. 
  7. Users agree that MIHIA may electronically collect, store and use the following personal information of Users: 
    1. email address
    2. mobile phone number
    3. closest city
    4. non-personal browsing habits and click patterns
    5. IP address
  8. MIHIA collects, stores and uses the abovementioned information for the following purposes: 
    1. to greet the User when he/she accesses the Site
    2. to inform the User of facts relating to his/her access and use of the Site and/or the Service
    3. to inform the User about competitions and special offers from MIHIA and/or its partners and/or affiliates
    4. to compile non-personal statistical information about browsing habits, click-patterns and access to the Site
    5. to verify the identity of the User when transacting with MIHIA
    6. to furnish information to Users regarding transactions, potential transactions and subscriptions.
  9. Information detailed above is collected either electronically by using cookies or is provided voluntarily by the User. Users may determine cookie use independently through their browser settings. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features that recognize your account as logged on and other Site features. Further, to help us tailor the Site to the needs and interests of our Users, or for other purposes, we may gather aggregate, permanently non-personally identifiable information via cookies. Examples include the type of Internet browser our Users are using, the frequency of visits to our site and which pages our Users viewed. We may share these aggregate statistics with others. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major web sites use them. 
  10. MIHIA may collect, maintain, save, compile and share any permanently de-identified information collected from Users, subject to the following provisions: 
    1. MIHIA shall not disclose personal information from Users, other than to its partners and affiliates, unless the User consents thereto
    2. MIHIA shall disclose information without the User's consent only where required to do so by law or any regulatory authority or where necessary to enforce MIHIA’s rights under these Terms
    3. MIHIA may compile, use, share and otherwise process any permanently de-identified information that does not relate and cannot be traced back to any specific individual.
  11. MIHIA owns and retains all rights to non-personal statistical information collected and compiled by MIHIA. 

## Do you need help?

If you have problem with using our site Dealfish.co.ug please see help.
